# H. K. NIMNAKA YASITH RAVISHAN KUMARADASA

5A, Polkotuwa Road, Rawathawatte, Moratuwa, Western Province, Sri Lanka • +94 77 0527 520 • nimnakakumaradasa1@gmail.com www.nimnakakumaradasa.com

# **SUMMARY**

As a Computer Science graduate specializing in Software Engineering and UI/UX design, I aim to contribute significantly to any organization. My goal is to excel by combining technical skills with user-centered design, continuously improving as a professional. I strive to be a distinguished leader, fostering innovation and creating exceptional digital experiences.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### UI/UX Designer | Frontend Developer, Nekfa Australia PVT LTD, Colombo 02 Nov 2023 - Present

- · Assist in the development of websites for clients using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, and WordPress.
- Moderate and develop dynamic digital content for interactive screens deployed at various locations.
- Collaborate with stakeholders to gather requirements and implement solutions that meet client needs effectively.
- Ensure websites are responsive and optimized for various devices for optimal performance.
- Developed the UK project <u>Cerinca</u> site.
- To view the official websites of the Negombo Municipal Council (Sri Lanka), the Kalutara Municipal Council (Sri Lanka) and the Attanagalla Pradeshiya Sabha (Sri Lanka).

# Information Security Intern, Hemas Holdings PLC, Colombo 02

Apr 2023 - Nov 2023

- · Assisted in the monitoring of Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) scenarios and notified them relevant SBUs'/parties and recommended actions to address potential security incidents.
- Proficiently utilized ManageEngine within a ServiceDesk Plus framework to manage ticket requests and inquiries. Ensured prompt issue resolution and provided exemptional support for end-users.
- Conducted a comprehensive evaluation and comparison of various Web Application Firewalls (WAF) along with their distributor and suppliers.
- · Applied design skills to create infographics and posters for company related events and innovative security awareness campaigns.
- Developed a Python script to convert .txt files to .log format, enhancing data processing and automation capabilities.

# Data Entry Analyst, Horizon College, Malabe, Colombo

Oct 2020 - Nov 2020

- Entered employee salary data and student details to the SAP system.
- Helped SAP team in finalizing data documents.

### **SOCIAL**













#### **EDUCATION**

### Bachelors of Computer Science Major in Software Engineering

Jan 2020 - Feb 2024

Edith Cowan University, Colombo, Sri Lanka

• Successfully completed the Bachelor's in Computer Science degree at Edith Cowan University.

# Diploma in Software Engineering

Aug 2020 - Nov 2021

Australian College of Business & Technology

• Successfully completed the Diploma Level of Computer Science.

# Diploma in Adobe Photoshop

2015

New Sense Education Centre, Moratuwa, Sri Lanka

• Successfully completed the Diploma Level of Computer Science.

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Project Management, MS Office, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, Figma, CorelDraw, HTML/CSS/JavaScript, React
- Soft Skills: Communication, Teamwork, Problem-Solving, Time Management
- · Languages: English, Sinhala
- Interests: Drawing, Singing, Cooking, Product Design, Dancing, Video Editing, Acting
- Certifications: Figma for UX Design, Web Development, More on LinkedIn

#### **VOLUNTEER WORKS**

Assistant Treasurer & Media Head: Students' Activity Council of ACBT
 Mar 2021 - Jan 2023

• Event Organizer & Design: Pearl Protectors

Apr 2021 - Dec 2023

• Media Unit: Young Zoologist Association of National Zoological Gardens

Dec 2019

#### **NON-RELATED REFREES**

- Mrs. Niresha Udayaratne | Assistant General Manager | Admin & HR agm@nekfa.com | (+94) 71 754 4364 | Nekfa Australia Pvt Ltd.
- Mr. Niroshan Tharanga | Cyber Security Manager | Information Security niroshan.groupit@hemas.com | (+94) 71 110 7717 | Hemas Holdings PLC
- Mr. Rukshi Rushan | Manager | Business Intelligence & Analytics <u>rukshi.groupit@hemas.com</u> | (+94) 76 227 3634 | Hemas Holdings PLC